Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - S
        - Speedy J - A shocking hobby, 2000; SR-25132; Speedy J (Box 442)
          Catalog # MUSDJ 073-0; A-side Matrix # MUS DJ 73-0 A
          NovaMute
        - Speedy J - Pullover, 1992; SR-25133; Speedy J (Box 442)
          Catalog # DOS 021; A-side Matrix # DOS-021-A
        - Speedy J - Pullover, 1995; SR-25134; Speedy J (Box 442)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # DOS-021-A
        - Spencer, J. - U should be mine, 1995; SR-25135; Spencer, J. (Box 442)
          Catalog # 374631339; A-side Matrix # 37463 1339 1 A SP1
          MoJazz
        - Spencer, Tracie - Hide and seek, 1988; SR-25136; Spencer, Tracie; Woolfolk, Andrew P. (Box 442)
          Catalog # V-15397; A-side Matrix # V-1-15397-101120-22 0 B-32168-Z2 21706
        - Spencer, Tracie - Hide and seek, 1988; SR-25137; Spencer, Tracie; Woolfolk, Andrew P. (Box 442)
        - Sphinx - Sphinx, 1977; SR-25138; Sphinx (Box 442)
          Catalog # NBLP 7077 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7077AS CP-1
        - Spice - You're so nice (Latin spice), 1983; SR-25139; Spice (Box 442)
          Catalog # JD 1 9040; A-side Matrix # JD-1-9040-SA
        - Spicer, Jimmy - The bubble bunch, 1982; SR-25140; Spicer, Jimmy; Benitez, John "Jellybean"; Blow, Kurtis; Simmons, Russell (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-25141. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # MDS-4017; A-side Matrix # MDS 4017-A
          Mercury
        - Spicer, Jimmy - The bubble bunch, 1982; SR-25141; Spicer, Jimmy; Benitez, John "Jellybean"; Blow, Kurtis; Simmons, Russell (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-25140. Multiple copies.
        - Spicer, Jimmy - Adventures of Super Rhyme (Rap), 1980; SR-25142; Spicer, Jimmy (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-25143. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # DA 1001; A-side Matrix # DA 1001
          Dazz Records